familyfriendpoems.com 2010-12-30

# Privacy Policy - FamilyFriendsPoems.com

* * *

Family Friend Poems is committed to protecting your privacy and developing features that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Family Friend Poems Web Site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Family Friend Poems website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information  
There is information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Family Friend Poems. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Family Friend Poems for the operation of the website, to maintain quality of the website, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Family Friend Poems Website.  

Use of your Personal Information  
Family Friends Poems collects and uses your personal information to operate the FamilyFriendsPoems.com website. Family Friend Poems also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Family Friend Poems.

Family Friend Poems keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Family Friend Poems, in order to determine what Family Friend Poems webpages are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Family Friend Poems to visitors whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Family Friend Poems Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Family Friend Poems or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Family Friend Poems; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Family Friend Poems, or the public.

Use of Cookies

The Family Friend Poems website uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies _cannot_ be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Family Friend Poems pages, or register with Family Friend Poems website, a cookie helps Family Friend Poems to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as contact preferences, login and passwords, and so on. When you return to the same Family Friend Poems website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Family Friend Poems features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Family Friend Poems website.

Ad Servers Privacy

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of: [Value Click Media](http://www.valueclickmedia.com/webuser_privacy.shtml), [Casale Media](http://www.casalemedia.com/privacy.html), [TribalFusion](http://www.exponential.com/who-we-are/privacy-policy.jsp) and [Burst Media](http://www.burstmedia.com/privacy.asp)  
You can opt-out of receiving Cookies from third party advertising networks through the [Network Advertising Initiatives cookie opt-out page](http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

We serve ads from third-party advertising companies who may collect information about your preferences when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Contact Information

Family Friend Poems welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Family Friend Poems has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Family Friend Poems using our Contact Us Form. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
